- Are you just getting home?
- Yeah.
(Sheldon:)That's a good sign, right?
(Penny:)Oh, yeah.
(Sheldon:)I'm so proud of you!
(Sheldon:)You sold yourself out
(Sheldon:)like a common streetwalker!
(Leonard:)No, I didn't do it
for the money.
(Sheldon:)She stiffed you?
(Penny:)I believe that's what
your roommate did to her.
What?!
(Penny:)Again, read the
book we gave you.
(Leonard:)No, I mean,
I-I got the money first.
(Sheldon:)Smart. Get paid up front.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I think you have a real
knack for gigolo work, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Uh...
(Leonard:)I'm gonna go lie down.
That's a good idea;
get your rest.
(Sheldon:)There are a lot more
rich old ladies out there,
(Sheldon:)and Daddy needs
a new linear accelerator.
(Sheldon:)And I thought he didn't learn anything
from his relationship with you.
(Mrs Latham:)Hey!
(Sheldon:)Another compliment!
(Sheldon:)Learn to recognize them.
(Seibert:)Ah, there he is!
(Seibert:)The man of the hour!
(Seibert:)He took one for the team!
(Leonard:)I didn't do it
for the money!
(Seibert:)Keep telling yourself that--
it makes it easier.
(Seibert:)Trust me, I know.
(Raj:)Cool, buddy!
That's awesome!
Yeah!
How was she?